Indiana University President's Office Correspondence, 1913-1937 C286
Indiana University Archives
- Subject files, 1913-1937 (Box 1)
  - Man (Box 167)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 167)
  - Mana-Manl, 1913-1923 (Box 167)
  - Manchester College (Box 167)
    - 1913-1926 (Box 167)
    - 1926-1928 (Box 167)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 167)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 167)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 167)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 167)
    - 1932-1934 (Box 167)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 167)
  - Manes, Professor Alfred, 1936-1937 (Box 167)
  - Manm, 1919-1920 (Box 167)
  - Mann (Box 167)
    - 1913-1924 (Box 167)
    - 1924-1930 (Box 167)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 167)
  - Mano-Manz, 1914-1923 (Box 167)
  - Mao-Maq, 1913-1923 (Box 167)
  - Mar (Box 167)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 167)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 167)
  - Mar (Box 168)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 168)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 168)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 168)
    - 1928-1930 (Box 168)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 168)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 168)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 168)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 168)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 168)
  - Mara-Marc, 1913-1923 (Box 168)
  - March—M-L, 1913-1914 (Box 168)
  - Mard-Marj, 1913-1923 (Box 168)
  - Marine Biological Laboratory, 1917-1919 (Box 168)
  - Marion College, 1927-1937 (Box 168)
  - Mark (Box 168)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 168)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 168)
  - Mark-Marr, 1913-1923 (Box 168)
  - Marm, 1925-1936 (Box 168)
  - Mars (Box 168)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 168)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 168)
  - Marshall, Frances, 1915-1917 (Box 168)
  - Marshall, Thomas R., undated (Box 168)
  - Mart (Box 168)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 168)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 168)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 168)
  - Mart (Box 169)
    - 1926-1928 (Box 169)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 169)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 169)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 169)
    - 1932-1935 (Box 169)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 169)
  - Mart-Marz (Box 169)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 169)
    - 1916-1920 (Box 169)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 169)
  - Martin, J.B.H. (Box 169)
    - September-December 1932, January-June 1933 (Box 169)
    - June-September 1933 (Box 169)
    - 1933-1934, (2 folders) (Box 169)
    - 1934-1935, (2 folders) (Box 169)
  - Martin, J.B.H. (Box 170)
    - 1935-1936, (2 folders) (Box 170)
    - 1936-1937, (2 folders) (Box 170)
  - Martz, Professor Velorus, 1936-1937 (Box 170)
  - Mas (Box 170)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 170)
    - 1919-1924 (Box 170)
    - 1924-1928 (Box 170)
    - 1928-1933 (Box 170)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 170)
  - Mason, Ruby E.C., 1913-1918 (Box 170)
  - Mat (Box 170)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 170)
    - 1920-1925 (Box 170)
    - 1925-1929 (Box 170)
    - 1929-1933 (Box 170)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 170)
  - Mathematics (Box 170)
    - 1913-1914 (Box 170)
    - Teaching load, 1936-1937 (Box 170)
  - Matson, Ross, McCord and Clifford (Indianapolis, IN), 1935-1936 (Box 170)
  - Matt (Box 170)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 170)
    - 1927-1933 (Box 170)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 170)
  - Mau-Max, 1913-1923 (Box 171)
  - Mau (Box 171)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 171)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 171)
  - Maxwell, Juliette (Box 171)
    - 1913-1922 (Box 171)
    - 1922-1931 (Box 171)
  - May-Maz (Box 171)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 171)
    - 1919-1923 (Box 171)
  - May (Box 171)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 171)
    - 1927-1932 (Box 171)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 171)
  - May, Clarence E., 1917-1919 (Box 171)
  - McA (Box 171)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 171)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 171)
  - McA-McB (Box 171)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 171)
    - 1918-1919 (Box 171)
  - McA-McD, 1928-1929 (Box 171)
  - McB (Box 171)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 171)
    - 1929-1937 (Box 171)
  - McC (Box 171)
    - 1913-1914 (Box 171)
    - 1914-1917 (Box 171)
    - 1916-1918 (Box 171)
  - McC (Box 171)
    - 1918-1920 (Box 171)
    - 1920-1921 (Box 171)
    - 1921-1922 (Box 171)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 171)
  - McC (Box 172)
    - 1924-1927 (Box 172)
    - 1927-1930 (Box 172)
    - 1930-1934 (Box 172)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 172)
  - McCar (Box 172)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 172)
    - 1927-1931 (Box 172)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 172)
  - McCl (Box 172)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 172)
    - 1926-1929 (Box 172)
    - 1929-1933 (Box 172)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 172)
  - McCo (Box 172)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 172)
    - 1925-1927 (Box 172)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 172)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 172)
    - 1931-1934 (Box 172)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 172)
  - McCormack, Colonel W.S., 1918-1919 (Box 172)
  - McCr (Box 172)
    - 1923-1931 (Box 172)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 172)
  - McCray, Governor Warren T., 1920-1924 (Box 173)
  - McD (Box 173)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 173)
    - 1917-1922 (Box 173)
    - 1921-1925 (Box 173)
    - 1925-1929 (Box 173)
    - 1929-1933 (Box 173)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 173)
  - McDonald, Alice Nelson, 1920-1926 (Box 173)
  - McDonald, James Grover (Box 173)
    - 1913-1922 (Box 173)
    - 1917-1918 (Box 173)
  - McE (Box 173)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 173)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 173)
  - McE-McF (Box 173)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 173)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 173)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 173)
  - McEwan, Eula Davis, 1917-1925; undated (Box 173)
  - McF (Box 173)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 173)
    - 1928-1932 (Box 173)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 173)
  - McG (Box 173)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 173)
    - 1920-1927 (Box 173)
    - 1927-1933 (Box 173)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 173)
  - McGonagle, Charles Austin, 1921-1931 (Box 173)
  - McGoveny, D.O., 1917-1918 (Box 173)
  - McGr (Box 173)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 173)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 173)
  - McGuire and Shook (Indianapolis), 1935-1937 (Box 173)
    - 1936 (Box 173)
    - January - February 1937 (Box 173)
    - March - April 1937 (Box 173)
    - May - September 1937 (Box 173)
  - McH, 1923-1937 (Box 174)
  - McH-McI (Box 174)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 174)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 174)
  - McI (Box 174)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 174)
    - 1927-1932 (Box 174)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 174)
  - McK (Box 174)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 174)
    - 1919-1920 (Box 174)
    - 1920-1924 (Box 174)
    - 1924-1927 (Box 174)
    - 1927-1930 (Box 174)
    - 1930-1933 (Box 174)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 174)
  - McKee, Homer Company, 1920-1921 (Box 174)
  - McL (Box 174)
    - 1913-1921 (Box 174)
    - 1919-1924 (Box 174)
    - 1921-1927 (Box 174)
    - 1927-1931 (Box 174)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 174)
  - McL-Md, 1928-1929 (Box 174)
  - McM (Box 174)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 174)
    - 1924-1928 (Box 174)
    - 1928-1932 (Box 174)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 174)
  - McMahan, Adah, 1913-1935 (Box 174)
  - McMillin, Alvin (Bo), 1936-1937 (Box 174)
  - McN (Box 175)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 175)
    - 1927-1932 (Box 175)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 175)
  - McN-McZ (Box 175)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 175)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 175)
  - McNutt, Paul V. (Box 175)
    - 1910-1921 (Box 175)
    - 1922-1924 (Box 175)
    - 1925 (Box 175)
    - 1926 (Box 175)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 175)
    - 1929 (Box 175)
    - 1930 (Box 175)
    - 1931 (Box 175)
    - 1932 (Box 175)
    - 1933 (Box 175)
    - 1934 (Box 175)
    - 1935 (Box 175)
    - Bust, 1935-1936 (Box 175)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 175)
  - McNutt, Ruth J. (Box 175)
    - 1928-1937 (Box 175)
    - Notes for President H.B Wells, 1936-1937 (Box 175)
    - c. 1937 (Box 175)
  - McO, 1923-1925 (Box 175)
  - McO-McQ, 1929-1937 (Box 175)
  - McP, 1923-1937 (Box 175)
  - McQ, 1923-1929 (Box 175)
  - McQuillin, Henry C., 1929-1930 (Box 175)
  - McR (Box 175)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 175)
    - 1930-1936 (Box 175)
  - McS, 1925-1937 (Box 175)
  - McT, 1923-1937 (Box 175)
  - McV, 1923-1930 (Box 175)
  - McV and McW, 1930-1937 (Box 175)
  - McW, 1923-1930 (Box 175)
  - McVey, F.B., 1913-1918 (Box 175)
  - Me (Box 175)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 175)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 175)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 175)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 175)
    - June-September 1926-1927 (Box 175)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 175)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 175)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 175)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 175)
  - Me (Box 176)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 176)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 176)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 176)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 176)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 176)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 176)
  - Me-Mn, 1928-1929 (Box 176)
  - Mea-Mec, 1913-1923 (Box 176)
  - Meal Tickets, 1928-1929 (Box 176)
  - Med-Mee (Box 176)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 176)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 176)
  - Medical School Building, 1918-1923 (Box 176)
  - Medical School (Box 176)
    - undated (Box 176)
    - Miscellaneous, 1913-1921 (Box 176)
  - See Also: School of Medicine (Box 176)
  - Medical Center—statistical report, 1936 (Box 176)
  - Medicine, School of (Box 176)
    - Survey, 1910 (Box 176)
    - Report, 1936-1937 (Box 176)
  - Medicine, School of and Hospital reports, 1924-1929 (Box 294)
  - I.U. Medical Center—report of the administrator (Box 176)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 294)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 294)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 294)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 176)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 176)
  - Mef-Meh, 1913-1923 (Box 176)
  - Mef-Mek, 1917-1918 (Box 176)
  - Meh, 1923-1937 (Box 176)
  - Mei-Mek, 1913-1923 (Box 176)
  - Meiklejohn, Alexander, 1913-1917 (Box 176)
  - Mel (Box 176)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 176)
    - 1928-1933 (Box 176)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 176)
  - Mel-Mem, 1913-1923 (Box 176)
  - Mellett, Don R. (Box 176)
    - 1913-1914, 1923-1924 (Box 176)
    - Memorial Tablet Campaign, 1926-1928 (Box 176)
  - Melville, Elizabeth, 1917 (Box 176)
  - Memorials, 1918-1919 (Box 176)
  - Memorial Campaign Fund, 1921 (Box 176)
  - Memorial Residence Hall, 1927 (Box 176)
  - Memorial Stadium (10th St.) Dedication, 1924-1926 (Box 176)
  - Men-Meq (Box 177)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 177)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 177)
  - Dr. Mendenhall (O.B.), 1925-1926 (Box 177)
  - Menger, Frederick, 1922-1937 (Box 177)
  - Mer (Box 177)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 177)
    - 1917-1922 (Box 177)
    - 1922-1927 (Box 177)
    - 1927-1932 (Box 177)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 177)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype Company, 1913-1915 (Box 177)
  - Merrill, Winfred (Box 177)
    - 1919-1924 (Box 177)
    - 1924-1928 (Box 177)
    - 1928-1932 (Box 177)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 177)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 177)
  - Mes (Box 177)
    - 1913-1922 (Box 177)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 177)
    - 1928-1937 (Box 177)
  - Met-Mex, 1913-1923 (Box 177)
  - Mexican Border Service—benefit fund for enlisted IU students, 1915-1916 (Box 177)
  - Mey (Box 177)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 177)
  - Mey (Box 178)
    - 1927-1932 (Box 178)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 178)
  - Mey-Mez (Box 178)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 178)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 178)
  - Mezes, S.E., 1913-1918 (Box 178)
  - Mi (Box 178)
    - 1915-1916 (Box 178)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 178)
    - 1925-1927 (Box 178)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 178)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 178)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 178)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 178)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 178)
  - Mia-Mic (Box 178)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 178)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 178)
  - Miami, University of (Box 178)
    - 1913-1924 (Box 178)
    - 1924-1929 (Box 178)
    - 1929-1932 (Box 178)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 178)
  - Michigan, University of (Box 178)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 178)
    - 1917-1922 (Box 178)
    - 1919-1920 (Box 178)
    - 1922-1924 (Box 178)
  - Michigan, University of (Box 179)
    - 1925-1927 (Box 179)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 179)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 179)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 179)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 179)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 179)
  - Michigan State (Normal College), 1922-1923 (Box 179)
  - Microscope rental list, 1928-1929 (Box 179)
  - Mid (Box 179)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 179)
    - 1928-1933 (Box 179)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 179)
  - Mid-Mik (Box 179)
    - 1913-1923 (Box 179)
    - 1916-1917 (Box 179)
  - Midland Chair & Seating Company, 1913-1914 (Box 179)
  - Miehle Printing Press & Manufacturing Company, 1913-1914 (Box 179)
  - Mil (Box 179)
    - 1913-1915 (Box 179)
    - 1915-1917 (Box 179)
    - 1917-1919 (Box 179)
    - 1919-1920 (Box 179)
    - 1921-1922 (Box 179)
    - 1922-1923 (Box 179)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 179)
    - 1927-1932 (Box 179)
  - Mil (Box 180)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 180)
  - Milam, Carl H.—library lists for children, 1925-1926 (Box 180)
  - Mil-Mis, 1920-1921 (Box 180)
  - Mileage and expense, 1936-1937 (Box 180)
  - Military education, 1931-1935 (Box 294)
  - Military correspondence, 1915-1917 (Box 180)
  - Military department, 1926 (Box 180)
  - Military law, undated (Box 180)
  - Committee on military matters—WWI (Box 180)
    - A-C, undated (Box 180)
    - D-J, undated (Box 180)
    - K-Q, undated (Box 180)
    - R-Z, undated (Box 180)
  - Milk Inspection, 1929 (Box 180)
  - Mill (Box 180)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 180)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 180)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 180)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 180)
    - May-September 1926-1927 (Box 180)
    - May-October 1927-1928 (Box 180)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 180)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 180)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 180)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 180)
  - Mill (Box 181)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 181)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 181)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 181)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 181)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 181)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 181)
  - Millcreek Distilling Company, 1913-1918 (Box 181)
  - Miller, Dailey and Thompson, 1924-1925 (Box 181)
  - Miller, Dorothy Lucille, 1927-1928 (Box 181)
  - Miller, John A., 1914-1937 (Box 181)
  - Miller Lock Company, 1914-1915 (Box 181)
  - Miller, Wilbert Eugene, 1936-1937 (Box 181)
  - Milles, 1936 (Box 181)
  - Millis, W.A., 1913-1918 (Box 181)
  - Mim-Mis (Box 181)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 181)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 181)
  - Min (Box 181)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 181)
    - 1928-1933 (Box 181)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 181)
  - Minnesota, University of (Box 181)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 181)
    - 1918-1921 (Box 181)
    - 1921-1925 (Box 181)
    - 1925-1928 (Box 181)
    - 1928-1931 (Box 181)
  - Minnesota, University of (Box 182)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 182)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 182)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 182)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 182)
  - Mississippi, University of, 1917-1918 (Box 182)
  - Missouri, University of (Box 182)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 182)
    - 1919-1925 (Box 182)
    - 1925-1931 (Box 182)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 182)
  - Mit (Box 182)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 182)
    - 1926-1929 (Box 182)
    - 1928-1933 (Box 182)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 182)
  - Mit-Miz (Box 182)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 182)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 182)
  - Mitchell Hall—remodeling and equipment for Sociology Department, 1936-1937 (Box 182)
  - Mo (Box 182)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 182)
    - 1926-1929 (Box 182)
    - 1929-1933 (Box 182)
  - Mo (Box 183)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 183)
  - Mo-Mx, 1928-1929 (Box 183)
  - Moa-Moh (Box 183)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 183)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 183)
  - Moenkhaus, W.J. (Box 183)
    - 1913-1921 (Box 183)
    - 1921-1926 (Box 183)
    - 1926-1930 (Box 183)
    - 1930-1934 (Box 183)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 183)
  - Moffatt, J.E., 1926; 1934-1937 (Box 183)
  - Moh (Box 183)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 183)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 183)
  - Moi-Mol, 1913-1923 (Box 183)
  - Molby, Fred A., 1913-1917 (Box 183)
  - Mom-Mon (Box 183)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 183)
    - 1917-1920 (Box 183)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 183)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 183)
  - Mon (Box 183)
    - 1925-1928 (Box 183)
    - 1928-1931 (Box 183)
  - Mon (Box 183)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 183)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 183)
  - Monnet, J.C., 1913-1915 (Box 183)
  - Monon Railway (Box 183)
    - 1913-1921 (Box 183)
    - 1921-1927 (Box 183)
    - 1927-1936 (Box 183)
  - Montana, University of (Box 183)
    - 1913-1921 (Box 183)
    - 1921-1928 (Box 183)
  - Montana, University of (Box 184)
    - 1928-1935 (Box 184)
  - Moo (Box 184)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 184)
    - 1928-1932 (Box 184)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 184)
  - Moo-Mop (Box 184)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 184)
    - 1916-1920 (Box 184)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 184)
  - Moor (Box 184)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 184)
    - 1925-1927 (Box 184)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 184)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 184)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 184)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 184)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 184)
  - Moore, Arthur—buildings and grounds, 1936-1937 (Box 184)
  - Moore, Harold E.—Teachers Placement Bureau, 1936-1937 (Box 184)
  - Moore, Henry Hays, 1931-1934 (Box 184)
  - Moore, Wilma, 1933-1934 (Box 184)
  - Moore's Hill College, 1913-1917 (Box 184)
  - Mor (Box 184)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 184)
    - 1927-1930 (Box 184)
    - 1930-1934 (Box 184)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 184)
  - Mora-Morp (Box 185)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 185)
    - 1918-1921 (Box 185)
    - 1921-1923 (Box 185)
  - Morg (Box 185)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 185)
    - 1927-1930 (Box 185)
    - 1930-1933 (Box 185)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 185)
  - Morgan, Theodore J., 1926 (Box 185)
  - Morr (Box 185)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 185)
    - 1926-1928 (Box 185)
    - 1928-1930 (Box 185)
    - 1930-1933 (Box 185)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 185)
  - Morr-Morz (Box 185)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 185)
    - 1916-1920 (Box 185)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 185)
  - Morris, George D., 1916-1919 (Box 185)
  - Mors, 1927-1937 (Box 185)
  - Morton, Clifford M H, 1930-1935 (Box 185)
  - Mos (Box 185)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 185)
    - 1927-1930 (Box 185)
    - 1930-1933 (Box 185)
  - Mos (Box 186)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 186)
  - Mos-Mot (Box 186)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 186)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 186)
  - Mosaic Tile Company, 1915 (Box 186)
  - Mottier, D.M. (Box 186)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 186)
    - 1919-1925 (Box 186)
    - 1925-1930 (Box 186)
    - 1931-1934 (Box 186)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 186)
  - Mottos, 1920 (Box 186)
  - Mou (Box 186)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 186)
    - 1928-1933 (Box 186)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 186)
  - Mou-Moz (Box 186)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 186)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 186)
  - Mr, undated (Box 186)
  - Mu (Box 186)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 186)
    - 1926-1929 (Box 186)
    - 1929-1932 (Box 186)
    - 1932-1935 (Box 186)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 186)
  - Mua-Muk, 1913-1923 (Box 186)
  - Muhlhauser, Captain, 1917-1918 (Box 186)
  - Mul (Box 186)
    - 1913-1921 (Box 186)
    - 1921-1926 (Box 186)
    - 1926-1929 (Box 186)
    - 1929-1932 (Box 186)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 186)
  - Mum-Mup, 1914-1923 (Box 186)
  - Mun (Box 186)
    - 1913-1914, 1921-1927 (Box 186)
  - Mun (Box 187)
    - 1927-1932 (Box 187)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 187)
  - Muncie Normal Institute, 1913-1917 (Box 187)
  - Mundy, Charles, 1923-1924 (Box 187)
  - Munro, Edna F. (Box 187)
    - 1928-1931 (Box 187)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 187)
  - Mur (Box 187)
    - 1913-1922 (Box 187)
    - 1922-1927 (Box 187)
    - 1927-1931 (Box 187)
    - 1931-1934 (Box 187)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 187)
  - Murphy, 1913-1923 (Box 187)
  - Murr (Box 187)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 187)
    - 1928-1933 (Box 187)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 187)
  - Murray State (Normal School, Teachers' College), 1926-1933 (Box 187)
  - Mus-Muz, 1913-1923 (Box 187)
  - School of Music Building—correspondence regarding construction, 1935-1937 (Box 187)
  - My (Box 187)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 187)
    - 1917-1922 (Box 187)
    - 1922-1925 (Box 187)
    - 1925-1928 (Box 187)
    - 1928-1931 (Box 187)
    - 1931-1934 (Box 187)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 187)
  - Myers, Burton Dorr (School of Medicine) (Box 188)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 188)
    - 1917-1918 (Box 188)
    - 1919 (Box 188)
    - 1920 (Box 188)
    - 1921 (Box 188)
    - 1922 (Box 188)
    - 1923 (Box 188)
    - 1924 (Box 188)
    - 1925 (Box 188)
    - 1926 (Box 188)
    - 1927 (Box 188)
    - 1928 (Box 188)
    - 1929 (Box 188)
    - 1930 (Box 188)
    - 1931 (Box 188)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 188)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 188)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 188)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 188)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 188)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 188)
  - N (Box 188)
    - 1913-1922 (Box 188)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 188)
    - 1926-1929 (Box 188)
  - N (Box 189)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 189)
    - 1931-1934 (Box 189)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 189)
  - Naa-Nal, 1913-1923 (Box 189)
  - Na-Nn, 1928-1929 (Box 189)
  - Nafe, 1914-1923 (Box 189)
  - Nam-Nas, 1913-1923 (Box 189)
  - Nansen, Fridtjof, 1929 (Box 189)
  - Nat (Box 189)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 189)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 189)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 189)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 189)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 189)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 189)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 189)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 189)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 189)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 189)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 189)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 189)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 189)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 189)
  - Nat-Naz (Box 189)
    - 1913-1915 (Box 189)
  - Nat-Naz (Box 190)
    - 1915-1917 (Box 190)
    - 1917-1919 (Box 190)
    - 1919-1921 (Box 190)
    - 1921-1922 (Box 190)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 190)
  - National City Company, 1917-1919 (Box 190)
  - National Advisory Committee on Education, undated (Box 190)
  - National Association of State Universities, 1904-1924 (Box 190)
  - National Companies (Box 190)
    - 1919-1926 (Box 190)
    - 1926-1932 (Box 190)
  - National Council of Teachers of English (Dr. C.S. Thomas), 1935-1936 (Box 190)
  - National Defense Committee at I.U., 1916-1918 (Box 190)
  - National Research Council (Box 190)
    - 1919-1921 (Box 190)
    - 1921-1923 (Box 190)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 190)
    - 1926-1930 (Box 190)
    - 1930-1934 (Box 190)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 190)
  - National Youth Administration (Box 190)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 190)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 190)
    - Bulletins, 1936-1937 (Box 190)
    - Official letters, 1936-1937 (Box 190)
  - Ne (Box 190)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 190)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 190)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 190)
    - 1926-1928 (Box 190)
  - Ne (Box 191)
    - 1928-1930 (Box 191)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 191)
    - 1932-1935 (Box 191)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 191)
  - Nea, 1913-1917 (Box 191)
  - Neal, E.H., 1913-1915 (Box 191)
  - Neal, Mabel E., 1917-1923 (Box 191)
  - Neal, Marcellus, 1929-1930 (Box 191)
  - Nea-Nek (Box 191)
    - 1917-1920 (Box 191)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 191)
  - Nebraska, University of (Box 191)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 191)
    - 1918-1924 (Box 191)
    - 1924-1930 (Box 191)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 191)
  - Needles, 1929 (Box 191)
  - Neff, Floyd R. (Box 191)
    - 1919-1923 (Box 191)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 191)
    - 1926-1929 (Box 191)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 191)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 191)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 191)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 191)
  - Neff, Robert E. (Box 191)
    - April-September 1924 (Box 191)
  - Neff, Robert E. (Box 192)
    - September 1924-March 1925 (Box 192)
    - April-September 1925 (Box 192)
    - September 1925-September 1926 (Box 192)
    - September 1926-May 1927 (Box 192)
    - June-September 1927 (Box 192)
    - September 1927-September 1928 (Box 192)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 192)
  - Negro (Miscellaneous), 1933-1937 (Box 192)
  - Nel-Net, 1913-1923 (Box 192)
  - Nel (Box 192)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 192)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 192)
  - Nelson, Mrs. Alice (Box 192)
    - 1926-September 1927 (Box 192)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 192)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 192)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 192)
    - September 1930-May 1931 (Box 192)
    - May-September 1931 (Box 192)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 192)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 192)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 192)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 192)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 192)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 192)
    - Correspondence with Joesting & Schilling (Box 193)
      - 1931-1932 (Box 193)
      - 1932-1933 (Box 193)
    - Items for Executive Committee & Board of Trustees (Box 193)
      - October 1931-January 1932 (Box 193)
      - February-May 1932 (Box 193)
      - June-September 1932 (Box 193)
      - October 1932-February 1933 (Box 193)
      - February-May 1933 (Box 193)
      - May-September 1933 (Box 193)
  - Nelson, Mrs. Alice (Box 193)
    - Items for Executive Committee & Board of Trustees (Box 193)
      - September 1933-February 1934 (Box 193)
      - March-May 1934 (Box 193)
      - June-September 1934 (Box 193)
      - September 1934-February 1935 (Box 193)
      - March-May 1935 (Box 193)
      - June-September 1935 (Box 193)
      - October-December 1935 (Box 193)
      - January-May 1936 (Box 193)
  - Nelson, Mrs. Alice (Box 194)
    - Items for Executive Committee & Board of Trustees (Box 194)
      - June-October 1936 (Box 194)
      - October 1936-January 1937 (Box 194)
      - February-March 1937 (Box 194)
      - April-July 1937 (Box 194)
  - Nelson, W.P. Company, 1936-1937 (Box 194)
  - Nem, 1927 (Box 194)
  - Neu-Nev, 1914-1923 (Box 194)
  - Nevada, University of, 1913-1919 (Box 194)
  - Neuenfeldt, E.R., 1916-1918 (Box 194)
  - New (Box 194)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 194)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 194)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 194)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 194)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 194)